<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Snake</string>

    <string name="nav_header_title">Aulia Nor Saputra</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">2010817210017@mhs.ulm.ac.id</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="selamat_datang">Welcome</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>

    <string name="desc_snake1">
        Malayopython reticulatus
        Maximum length exceeding 8.5 meters is non-toxic but has a strong grip so that its prey cannot escape.
    </string>

    <string name="desc_snake2">
        Eunectus
        Maximum length exceeding 8.43 meters is non-toxic but has a strong grip so that its prey cannot escape.
        </string>

    <string name="desc_snake3">
        Dendroaspis
        Maximum length exceeding 4.3 meters in addition to having a deadly venom, the mamba can move
        very fast and even exceed the speed of human running.
        </string>

    <string name="desc_snake4">
        Crotalus sp
        Maximum length exceeds 1.38 meters. Theuniqueness of this snake is that it attracts its prey
        by using the tip of its tail which vibratesto make its prey think that it is food. But when
        the prey approaches he will bite the prey and killit with the poison it has.
        </string>

    <string name="desc_snake5">
        Naja
        Maximum length exceeding 1.8 meters in addition to spreading venom through the bite of a cobra,
        it can also spit its venom out of its mouth which can cause blindness if it hits the eye.
        </string>

    <string name="desc_snake6">
        Vipera beruz
        Maximum length exceeds 90 centimeters despite having a relatively small size vipers are known
        to have deadly venom.
        </string>

    <string name="desc_snake7">
        Pytas korros
        Maximum length of more than 2.5 meters, the rice field snake or what is known as the rat-eating
        snake has no poison, but this snake is able to tightly wrap around the rat to make it easy to eat
        the rat.
        </string>

    <string name="desc_snake8">
        Hydrophiinae
        Maximum length exceeding 2.7 meters this snake can swim very fast in the water. In addition,
        sea snakes also have a deadly venom because 1 drop of its venom can kill 1800 people in just
        30 minutes.
        </string>

    <string name="desc_snake9">
        Acrochordus granulatus
        Maximum length exceeding 2.4 meters kadut snake is also a snake that lives in water but this
        snake does not have poison.
        </string>

    <string name="desc_snake10">
        Boa constrictor
        Maximum length exceeding 3.9 meters is non-toxic but has a strong grip so that its prey cannot escape.
        </string>

</resources>